<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Running Weight Loss</string>
    <string name="btn_begin">RUNS BEGIN</string>
    <string name="txt_weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="txt_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="txt_age">Age</string>
    <string name="btn_done">DONE</string>
    <string name="txt_detail">Input your accurate parameters to customize your training plan.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_result">Result</string>
    <string name="txt_time">Time</string>
    <string name="txt_run">Run</string>
    <string name="txt_kcal">Kcal</string>
    <string name="btn_start">START</string>
    <string name="btn_stop">STOP</string>
    <string name="btn_challenge">CHALLANGE</string>
    <string name="btn_history">HISTORY</string>
    <string name="btn_more">MORE</string>
    <string name="txt_congrat">Congrats! You have complete Day 1 Challenge!</string>


    <string name="day_X">DAY %s</string>
    <string name="X_completed">%s%% completed</string>
    <string name="total_time">Total Time</string>
    <string name="total_minute">15 Minute</string>
    <string name="calories_burn">Calories Burn</string>
    <string name="k_cal">1.5 Kcal</string>
    <string name="btn_end">End</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ready">ReadyActivity</string>


    <string name="drawer_title_day_x_plan">Day %s Plan</string>
    <string name="drawer_title_history">Exercise History</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_history_list">List History</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_history_graph">Graph History</string>
    <string name="drawer_title_tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_exercise_tutorial">Exercise Tutorial</string>
    <string name="drawer_title_more">More</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_pro_version">Pro + Remove Ads</string>
    <string name="drawer_title_miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_share">Share</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_rate">Rate us</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_contact">Contact us</string>
    <string name="drawer_item_about">About us</string>



    <string name="tip_olive_oil">Average Greek consumes more than 20 liters of olive oil a year, that why the spartan look so sexy and we have included in your meal plan today, check it out now!</string>
    <string name="tip_coffee">Coffee can specifically increase the burning of fat, by as much as 10% in obese individuals, but drinking too much will make you count sheep at the night, so follow our meal plan today to burn fat and sleep soundly tonight!</string>
    <string name="tip_almonds">Almonds consumed as snacks reduce hunger and desire to eat later in the day but try not to overconsume it, because it is soooo expensive. Almonds is included in our meal plan today, check it out now.</string>
    <string name="tip_brown_rice">Brown rice is an excellent source of dietary fibre, it tend to fill you up more and has been associated with decreased food intake and maintenance of a healthy body weight, so say no to racist and become a riceist, brown rice > white rice, check out our brown rice meal today!</string>
    <string name="tip_chicken_breast">Eating chicken breast, without breading or skin, helps you eat fewer calories and even burn extra calories for effective weight loss, transforming yourself into the nemesis of chicken breast is always the first step to shape your body, check out our chicken breast meal plan for today.</string>
    <string name="tip_brocolli">Broccoli is high in fiber, which aids in digestion, prevents constipation, maintains low blood sugar, and also helps in prevent cancer. So next time you meet a cancerous attitude person, feed them brocolli to make them shut up. Check out our brocolli meal plan today!</string>
    <string name="tip_apple"> An apple a day keeps the doctor away, because you won\'t be able to afford anything if you buy so many iphones, check out our meal plan today for cheaper apple meal.</string>
    <string name="tip_eggs">Whole eggs are among the most nutritious foods on the planet, containing a little bit of almost every nutrient we need. Not too eggciting huh, come check out our more eggciting meal plan today!</string>
    <string name="tip_mushrooms">Mushrooms are the only fruit or vegetable source of vitamin D and especially low in glycemic index which means it make you feel fuller for longer time. Super Mario\'s favourite. Check out our dish cooked with mushroom today.</string>
    <string name="tip_spinach">Spinach help you lose weight because they\'re low in calories but nutrient-dense. Although Popeye would have you believe it will bulk you up, actually spinach is the key to keep you slim. Check out our meal with spinach today.</string>
    <string name="tip_tomato_juice">According to the study, a daily glass of tomato juice can help trim your waistline. So we included it in our meal plan today and don\'t worry, you won\'t become a vampire.</string>
    <string name="tip_banana">Banana is effective in curbing your appetite and controlling the increased blood sugar levels in the body but don\'t feed it to the wild monkeys. Check out our meal plan today with banana.</string>
    <string name="tip_potato">A serving of potato contains only just 110 calories and having zero fat as well as zero cholestrol. According to the study, eating potato not gonna make you looks like a potato. Tap to check out our potato meal plan today.</string>
    <string name="tip_salmon_oil">Salmon oil can help to lower triglycerides in the blood and, therefore, reduce the amount of stored fat on your body. Thats why there are so many salmon oil supplements selling everywhere. Don\'t like eating supplements? Come check out our real tasty salmon meal today.</string>
    <string name="tip_papaya">Papaya is well known for its low fat, cholesterol free and low calorie nature. It also helps to enhance your digestive system and relieve constipation. It will be so fast that your collegue won\'t even notice you went to toilet. Come check out our meal plan with papaya today.</string>
    <string name="tip_oatmeal">The body digests oatmeal at a slower pace, keeping blood sugar levels steady, energy up, and hunger away. Perfect food for elderly, we know that you are only 18 year old, but oatmeal is still good for your body. Tap to see how to eat oatmeal tastily.</string>
    <string name="tip_strawberry">Strawberry contains Anthocyanins actually increase the body’s production of a hormone called adiponectin, which stimulates your metabolism and suppresses your appetite. What do you call a sad strawberry? Check out our meal plan for the answer!</string>
    <string name="tip_walnuts"> Eating a diet rich in walnuts can lead to the same amount of weight loss as a lower fat, higher carbohydrate diet and also walnuts are rich in polyunsaturated fats, which are beneficial to heart health and lower cholesterol. So remember to buy some Walnuts when you pass by Walmart. Check out our meal plan today which included walnuts.</string>
    <string name="tip_green_tea">Green tea, is packed with catechins, which help to promote weight loss by boosting your body\'s ability to metabolise lipids (fat). So, do you want to have a tea with me? Remember to check out today meal plan with green tea before our rendezvous.</string>
    <string name="tip_carrots">Carrots are mostly water and fiber to keep you hydrated and feeling full. You\'ll also get essential nutrients, such as vitamins A and K. Therefore start eating carrots now you little bunny. Check out our meal plan today with carrots.</string>
    <string name="tip_asparagus">As a natural diuretic, asparagus helps flush excess liquid, combating belly bulge. Keep going and you will eventually become slim like asparagus. Tap to see your meal plan today with asparagus.</string>
    <string name="tip_bell_pepper">Red peppers contain a molecule called capsaicin that is shown to increase your fat-burning rate and promote weight loss, also, (rrriiinnnggg.....) oops time to have some "bell" peppers, come check out our meal plan today</string>
    <string name="tip_avocados">Avocados tend to be high in fiber, about 7% by weight, which is very high compared to most other foods. Fiber can have various important benefits for weight loss and metabolic health. But if avocado is fruit, then is guacamole a smoothie? Come check out our diet plan with avocado today.</string>
    <string name="tip_green_bean">Adding green beans to the diet ensures a healthy supply of important nutrients without any extra calories and bean is funny. Tap to view our meal plan today with beans.</string>
    <string name="tip_lettuce">Lettuce has only 12 calories for one shredded cup and zero fat which make it a particularly effective diet food. The nickname of perfect weight loss food is not for nothing. Come to check out our meal plan with lettuce today.</string>
    <string name="tip_orange">Free radicals contribute to your body\'s aging process. The high levels of antioxidants found in oranges help to reduce damage to your skin caused by high levels of free radicals. A diet rich in oranges can thus result in fewer wrinkles and healthier-looking skin as you age. You want to slim down as well as looks younger at the same time, don\'t you? Come check out today meal plan.</string>
    <string name="tip_greek_yogurt">Greek yogurt can keep you fortified with essential nutrients and even help you lose weight, it has thicker texture with fewer carbohydrates and sugar, and more protein than regular yogurt. Btw, let me tell you a secret, greek yogurt is not only being sold at Greece. Check out our meal plan today on when is the best time having greek yogurt.</string>
    <string name="tip_celery">Celery is extremely low in calories and can be a valuable food to help you lose weight because of its ability to provide vital nutrients and to help regulate lipid (fat) metabolism, however not everyone can stand the aroma of it, I cant. Come check out our meal plan today for dishes with celery (also the alternative)</string>
    <string name="tip_prawn">Prawn has no guts, no spine and a head full of shit, but it\'s market value still high because of its nature of having very less calories as compared to most other meats and thus is very good for keeping the calorie count down and loose weight. Come check out our meal plan with prawn today.</string>
    <string name="tip_onion">Onion is a rich source of chromium. Deficiency of chromium slows down the body’s weight loss mechanism. In addition, the thermogenic effect of onion boosts fat burning. Hence, onion can help you in getting rid of the excess body weight. But try to avoid kiss after having it. Come check out our meal plan with onion today.</string>

    <string name="exercise_quote1">You cannot expect to achieve new goals or move beyond your present circumstances unless you change.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote2">Those who think they have not time for bodily exercise will sooner or later have to find time for illness.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote3">Every day do something that will inch you closer to a better tomorrow.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote4">You will never change your life until you change something you do daily.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote5">A strong positive attitude will create more miracles than any wonder drug.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote6">Progress is impossible without change and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote7">Believe while others are doubting.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote8">Failure is not fatal. Only failure to get back up is.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote9">You don’t drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote10">It’s in your moments of decision that your destiny is shaped.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote11">Most people fail, not because of lack of desire, but, because of lack of commitment.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote12">The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote13">People may doubt what you say, but they will believe what you do.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote14">Movement is a medicine for creating change in a person’s physical, emotional, and mental states.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote15">Too many people confine their exercise to jumping to conclusions, running up bills, stretching the truth, bending over backwards, lying down on the job, sidestepping responsibility and pushing their luck.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote16">Believe and act as if it were impossible to fail.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote17">A goal without a plan is just a wish.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote18">If you want to accomplish anything in life, you can’t just sit back and hope it will happen. You’ve got to make it happen.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote19">Motivation is what gets you started. Habit is what keeps you going.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote20">Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote21">The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote22">There are only two options regarding commitment; you’re either in or you’re out. There’s no such thing as life in-between.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote23">Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote24">Nothing will work unless you do.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote25">No matter who you are, no matter what you do, you absolutely, positively do have the power to change.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote26">People often say that motivation doesn’t last. Well, neither does bathing – that’s why we recommend it daily.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote27">Put all excuses aside and remember this: YOU are capable.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote28">Whenever you do a thing, act as if all the world were watching.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote29">You are braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think.</string>
    <string name="exercise_quote30">The future is always beginning now.</string>
</resources>
